

# **SHAILY GANDHI**

UX/UI designer

shaily.vercel.app

## CONTACT

shailymgandhi@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/shaily-gandhi

+31 6 84480755

### **SKILLS**

User research
User interviews
A/B testing
UX design
UI design
Prototyping and Wire-framing
Problem solving

Stakeholder management

#### **TOOLS**

Figma / Hotjar / Google Analytics / Jira / Miro / Adobe XD / Photoshop / Sketch

## **EDUCATION**

UX/UI Bootcamp Ironhack, Amsterdam 2021 - 2022

Bachelors of Architecture CEPT University, Ahmedabad 2007 - 2013

Student Exchange Program TUM, Munich. 2011

## **PROFILE**

With +9 yrs experience in the Design field, I am a designer dedicated to work towards achieving goals and to carefully create products that bring positive change into people's lives. My approach to design is grounded in user research & human experience to solve the small but significant problems, both for users & businesses.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## UX Designer | Basic-Fit

July 2023 - Current

- Took lead to improve the important user journeys for +4M users
- Conducted user testing sessions to get insights on the current product
- Improved Click-through rates based on the A/B tests results across several markets
- Develop user flows, create wireframes and deliver hi-fi prototypes
- Collaborated closely with devs, POs and design team

## All round UX/UI Designer | Tellow

July 2022 - June 2023

May 2022 - June 2022 (UX-UI design Internship)

- Translate complex issues into a clear story
- Provide conceptual and strategic advice on product development
- Develop user flows, create wireframes and deliver hi-fi prototypes
- Use research methods to analyze the users and understand the business needs
- Implement new product solutions with attractive designs
- · Setting up the design system and Library

# UX/UI part-time Designer | Ironhack

September 2021 - April 2022

- UX-UI design of a travel app- Motuu (Collaboration with a client, UX research, Wireframing, High Fidelity Prototype, Usability Testing, Desirability Testing, Style Guide)
- Design of a native ios Nutrition checking app
   Wireframing, High Fidelity Prototype, Usability Testing, Desirability Testing, Styleguide
- Editorial Design, Design of a responsive Web Magazine
   UX/UI Design, UX Research, Usability Testing, Responsive Design Guide

# Assistant Designer | KENK

April 2018 - October 2020

# Associate Designer | Keystone Architects

November 2015 - September 2017

# Junior Designer | Footprints E.A.R.T.H

October 2013 - September 2014